Like a beach villa.
Cute side
Ooh!
Very cool.
Just this one.
Tomitake, I'm buying a car.
Hello everyone!
I'm Suka Tomita from Hyugaizaka46!
Today is the third installment of Tomita Buying a Car.
For the third installment, here it is!
Ta-da!
Marumio Auto!
They have a lot of old cars!
Here we are at Marmio Auto!
Wow!
This old car...
I guess you could call them old history.
I guess you could say it's the history of old cars.
I wanted to buy the first one after having a better understanding of the various types of cars
I want to buy my first car after I have a better understanding of the history and the various types of old cars.
So today, I would like to go and look at old cars.
I hope you enjoy this video with me!
I'm off!
Today I don't know much about the most important places, so I'd like to ask someone to go around with me.
I'd like to go around with a little guidance, so let's go around first.
I wonder how old this one is.
When was this one made?
1999.
Heisei 11?
Two years before I was born.Two years before I was born.
So this is relatively recent?
Yes, it is.
Like this.
But I'm not familiar with it.
I guess you could call it an unfamiliar car.
This is a car called "Chaser".
The emblem is for the owner's exclusive use.
Oh, I see.
Chaser means "chase car.
Chaser?
Yeah, it jumps out at you in the shadows.
That's why it's like this.
Oh, it has a meaning.
I see.
Wow, but it's cute.
Heh~
I don't think I've ever seen tires like this before.
See?
They're shaped like tetrapods.
The wagon with the glasses is a model called Precuelle.
It's a special edition of the Colosse design.
Even the tire coils are a special version.
Heh~
This shape is amazing, isn't it?
But you don't see this color very often now, do you?
You don't see many of this color anymore.
This color is so cute!
I love it.
It's so cute!Wow, so cute!
Wow, Impressor!
Wow, it's so cute!
These two cars are so cute!
They're adorable.
Isn't it nice?
Wow, it's so low. It feels like it's been here forever.
Oh, this is cool.
This is cool. Wait, but I'm curious.
Wow, I'm curious about that one in the middle, too.
Oh, wow.
I'm missing an eye.
This is pretty popular, isn't it?
Maybe I'll see it more often.
Cute! I think it's absolutely adorable. I'm sure the girls will love it.
It's cute! Butte
Wow!
Wow, this is so cool! Isn't the color really austere?
Is this a 1994?
It's so cool!
May I take a look?
It's so beautiful!
Let me get in.
Oh, wow.
Amazing.
The scent... the scent...
It smells like the old days... or rather, a while ago.
It smells like the Heisei era. Wow, it's good.
I love it. I love it. I love it.Wow, I like it. I like it.
This is really nice, too. I could never do this with Bluetooth.
But maybe it's cute even if it takes a lot of work.
I'm thinking it's totally possible.
Thank you so much!
What a stylish Celica!
I like the angularity of it.
How old is this?
What year is this? 1986?
1986.
How long was the Showa period?
64 years.
Oh.
It will end in January of 1964.
Hou
I heard that, but it doesn't sound quite right.
Oh, I see.
Wow.
Wait, wait, wait, what's this?
Isn't this really cute?
No, I like this kind of thing.
I've seen this picture before in the second series.
I did this with the AE86.
Can I ride on it?
It's so cute!
It's a Carina.
What does 1984 mean?
I can't do the math.I can't do the math at all.
How long ago was the Showa period, 64?
And now the Heisei era?
Oh, 2021.
That's not good.
But how long ago was this?
Excuse me.
Wow!
Asial.
Oh!
Grandpa's house.
Excuse me
Oh, it's so soft!
The chair is so soft. Wow.
It's nice.
Wouldn't it be cool to ride in one of these?
I like it.
Does it have air conditioning?
Then it's fine.
I'm sensitive to heat.
How is it?
Well, I'll be inside.
Oh, really?
You know, women.
Teenagers.
Wow.
I might join them.
I'm crazy about it.
The more I ride, the more I like it.
the more I ride, the more I like it.I'm kind of starting to like it.
A car is a car, but...
I feel like it's something else.
When I first went to see SUVs.
And when I went to see a sports car...
I don't know.
It's like you're looking at something else.
I don't know how to put it.
I don't know.
It's like...
I don't know, like something salty or something.
I can't pronounce it.
Cute.
Hey, this one has high weather value.
Weather value and, well, there are many factors about Hachioji.
Oh, you mean like that.
Like the influence of manga.
That's right.
I'm a Nepoleño, so you're the eye-papa-papa.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's look at the back.
Wow, he's cute!
Let's look at the back, too.
I don't know, it's so attractive.
I guess I like the color.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Oh! Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.It's okay.
Is it okay if I do it before, sheet?
Oh! I like it.
I like it a lot.
You ready?
I'm gonna start the engine.
Oh, my gosh.
That's so good! The sound of this engine is going to be a trigger.
I love fast cars.
It's so cool!
Great!
wow stopping is good too
I love that it stops.
So cool!
It's so cool!
Wow, I kinda want one of these.
The more I look at it, the more I think
the more I see it, the more I like it.
I've been eyeing this one since it arrived.
Isn't this cool?
So cool!
This was on the market until about the 10th year of the Heisei era.
The business card says that it was on the market until the Heisei era.
But it's a good car because you can feel the old car.
Also, there are people who are surfers, aren't there?
That makes sense.
It certainly has the feel of being parked in front of a palm tree on the beach.
This wood grain book is originally attached to the car.
It's very nice.
Now, if you'll excuse me.Now, if you'll excuse me.
Cute.
So cute.
It's so cute.
Oh, my God.
This is super nice.
This is so cute!
This one.
This is so stylish!
It's really...
It's like a villa
Like a villa.
This place
This place is really stylish.
And it looks a little bit like...
It looks like chocolate.
Chocolate is so cute!
Wow, this is nice!
I love this!
It's definitely a manual.
Cars for eating and drinking...
Most of them are auto man-oisterers.
Is that right?
This is an Automan.
Then let's go with this one.
It's really on that level. It's so cute.
How much is this one?
It's a little bit...
Let's put it on the list.
It's really nice.It's soooo nice!
Thank you.
I'm sure you'd say I'm cool if I rode this.
You know, if I rode this...
I'd be like, "Oh my god, you're so cool! I'm gonna be a cool senior!
I'll probably hatch into a senior.
For the 4th graders.
What's this?
Seema.
It's a little creamy.
It's kind of luxurious, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, wow.
It's nice.
Oh, Skyline.
Oh, it's nice.
Oh, no.
No.
I can't forget that one.
What was it again?
Cedric Bagong.
Cedric Baggon. I can't forget Cedric Baggon.
It's all I can think about.
This one.
Cedric, Cedric Wagon.
The most important point is the wood-grain look of this car.
The brown inside... it's a shape that doesn't exist today.
It's because it's an old car.
It's because it's a car from this era.
It's a little different from the new cars of today.What is a little bit different from a new car nowadays?
It's been 30 years since the last new car.
Many people are a little concerned about breakdowns.
In terms of maintenance
If you don't maintain it well
You have to take good care of it.
I guess it's good that it takes so much time and effort.
Cedric wagon was so cute!
Maybe I'm just a meek person.
I knew it! Corolla Levin!
It's so cute!
I was completely attracted by its appearance.
Is this a manual transmission? Is this a manual? I could hear the engine.
It was great when you turned it on, but it was also great when you turned it off. Did you hear that?
I thought most old cars were manual.
I'd love to drive it on the beach.
It's no good.
Suki's got a lot more power than I thought she'd have.
I thought I would never be able to afford an old car, so I thought I would never be able to afford an old car.
I guess I'm more attached to it than I thought I would be.
It's so cute! It's so cute!
Back, back.
Wow, it's nice.
I'm really glad that I came here today because I really want to see an old car as an experience.
I'm not going to buy a car today!
I will not buy a car! I just want to say that I have seen a lot of cars, 1, 2, 3................
I've been thinking a lot about what kind of car I like, what kind of car I can realistically drive, and so on.
I have already decided on the car I want! It's decided!I have already decided on the car I want! I have decided!
So please look forward to the next episode!
If you enjoyed today's episode, please subscribe to the channel and click the "like" and "rate" buttons!
This is Suzuka Tomita from Hyugaizaka46! Old cars are the best!
Bye bye!